Guide to the Biographical Reference Collection, 1972-2004 UA.01.11.0004
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Biographical Files
  - Eldridge, Albert F. [Political Science] (Box 10)
  - Elion, Gertrude Belle. Nobel Prize. [Adjunct Professor of Experimental Medicine; Adjunct Associate Professor of Pharmacology] (Box 10)
  - Elkins, Heather [Divinity] (Box 10)
  - Ellis, C. P. (Box 10)
  - Elliott, William Whitfield [Math] (Box 10)
  - Ellis, H. M. [English] (Box 10)
  - Ellwood, Charles A. (Box 10)
  - El Naga, Sayed [Dining Hall] (Box 10)
  - Elsevier, Ernest [Engineering] (Box 10)
  - Emge, Walter G. (Box 10)
  - Ennis, Alana [Director of Public Safety] (Box 10)
  - Entman, Robert [Public Policy Studies] (Box 10)
  - Entremont, Philippe (Box 10)
  - Erickson, Carl J. [Psychology] (Box 10)
  - Eslinger, Richard [Divinity] (Box 10)
  - Espey, John [Lacrosse] (Box 10)
  - Epstein, Ann Wharton [Art] (Box 10)
  - Estes, E. Harvey, Jr. (Box 10)
  - Eulo, Ken [Playwright] (Box 10)
  - Evans, Lawrence "Larry" [Physics] (Box 10)
  - Everett, Robinson [Law] (Box 10)
  - Faribank, Henry [Physics] (Box 10)
  - Falcone, Carmen [Athletics] (Box 10)
  - Fara, Louis [Stone Setter] (Box 10)
  - Farmer, Dr. Paul (Box 10)
  - Farrar, Judity [Medical School Librarian] (Box 10)
  - Farris, Donn Michael [Divinity Library] (Box 10)
  - Fearing, Robert Beveridge [Administration] (Box 10)
  - Fein, John M. [Dean of Trinity Collige of Arts and Sciences] (Box 10)
  - Feinstein, John (Box 10)
  - Feinstein, Michael (Box 10)
  - Felker, Clay Schuette '51 (Box 10)
  - Ferguson, C. E. [Economics] (Box 10)
  - Ferguson, Oliver W. [English] and Joanne (Box 10)
  - Ferrari, Giovanni (Box 10)
  - Ferree-Clark, Nancy [Minister. Duke Chapel] (Box 10)
  - Ferriero, David S. [University Librarian and Vice-Provost for Library Affairs] (Box 10)
  - Ferry, Danny [Basketball. Retired Jersey, #35] (Box 10)
  - Few, William Preston
    - Family (Box 10)
    - Inauguration, Memorials, etc. (Box 10)
    - President (Box 10)
    - Speeches and writings (Box 10)
  - Fields, Charles Larry [Library] (Box 11)
  - Fields, Peggy '79 [see also: poster of Banks and Diamonds (basketball) on file] (Box 11)
  - Fillmore, Richard [ S. P. Duke Gardens] (Box 11)
  - Fish, Peter [Political Science] (Box 11)
  - Fish, Stanley [English] (Box 11)
  - Fischer, Rabbi Frank [Hillel Driector] (Box 11)
  - Fleishman, Joel L. [Administration] (Box 11)
  - Fletcher, A. J. (Box 11)
  - Flowers, Anne [Education] (Box 11)
  - Flowers, George Washington [Trustee] (Box 11)
  - Flowers, Robert Lee (Box 11)
  - Flowers, William Washington (Box 11)
  - Fluke, Don and Pepper [Zoology] (Box 11)
  - Fonda, Jane [visited Duke in 1970] (Box 11)
  - Forbus, Wiley D. [Medical Center - Pathology] (Box 11)
  - Forlines, John A., Jr. (Box 11)
  - Fortney, Lloyd R. [Physics] (Box 11)
  - Foster, William E. [Atheltics] (Box 11)
  - Fowler, David W. (Box 11)
  - Fowler, Edward [International Studies] (Box 11)
  - Fowlie, Wallace [French] (Box 11)
  - Fowlkes, H. Lee [Drama] (Box 11)
  - Fox, Adrienne [Law] (Box 11)
  - Fox, Richard G. [Anthropology] (Box 11)
  - Francis, Garrick [Administration] (Box 11)
  - Franklin, John Hope [History] (Box 11)
  - Franklin: Race Commission (Box 11)
  - Franks, Carl [Football] (Box 11)
  - Fraser-Reid, Bert [Chemistry] (Box 11)
  - Frazee, Wallace (Box 11)
  - Fridovich, Irwin [Biochemistry] (Box 11)
  - Fried, Lee (Box 11)
  - Friedl, Ernestine [Anthropology] (Box 11)
  - Friedrich, John A. [Physical Education] (Box 11)
  - Fulkerson, Mary McClintock [Divinity School] (Box 11)
  - Fuller, Howard (Box 11)
  - Fuller, J. Peyton [Administration] (Box 11)
  - Funderburk, M. Laney, Jr. [Administration] (Box 11)
  - Fuqua, J. B. [Endowment] (Box 11)
  - Furbish, William J. [Geology] (Box 11)
  - Furlow, John [Athletics] (Box 11)
  - Fuson, Robert L. (Box 11)
  - Fyfe, Charles R. [Administration-Business] (Box 11)
  - Gaines, Jane [Literature/English] (Box 11)
  - Galifianakis, Nick (Box 11)
  - Gallie, Tom (Box 11)
  - Gann, Pamela B. [Law] (Box 11)
  - Gannaway, W. T. [Latin. Trinity College] (Box 11)
  - Garber, Paul Neff [Divinity School] (Box 11)
  - Garci-Gomez, Miguel [Romance Languages] (Box 11)
  - Garg, Devendra [Engineering] (Box 11)
  - Garrard, Anne Walker (Box 11)
  - Garrow, David J. (Box 11)
  - Gaspar, David Barry [History] (Box 11)
  - Gates, Henry Louis, Jr. [English] (Box 11)
  - Gates, Melinda French [Board of Trustees] (Box 11)
  - Gaudet, Pete [Sports] (Box 11)
  - Gavins, Raymond [History] (Box 11)
  - Gearreald, Karen [Law] (Box 11)
  - Gehman, W. Scott. Gehman, Ila H. (Box 11)
  - George, Rhett, Jr. (Box 11)
  - George, Thelma (Box 11)
  - Georgiade, D. Nicholas (Box 11)
  - Gerber, Linda H. (Box 11)
  - Gerard, Gerry [Basketball Coach] (Box 11)
  - Gereffi, Gary (Box 11)
  - Gergen, David (Box 11)
  - Gergen, John J. [Math] (Box 11)
  - Geweke, John F. [Economics] (Box 11)
  - Giannini, Richard (Box 11)
  - Gibbons, Jeffery [Guitarist] (Box 11)
  - Gibson, Elizabeth (Box 11)
  - Gibson, Josh (Box 11)
  - Giddings, Paula J. [Women's Studies] (Box 11)
  - Gifford, James [Community and Family Medicine] (Box 11)
  - Gilbert, Allan H. [English] (Box 11)
  - Gilbert, K. C. (Box 11)
  - Gilbert, Katherine E. [Philosophy] (Box 11)
  - Giles Sisters [Trinity Graduates] (Box 12)
  - Gill, William F. [Latin, Trinity College] (Box 12)
  - Gillham, Nicholas W. [Zoology] (Box 12)
  - Gillis, S. Malcolm (Box 12)
  - Gilmore, George (Box 12)
  - Gilmore, Jimmy [Music] (Box 12)
  - Gionta, Ralph L. [Facility Planning] (Box 12)
  - Gish, Annabeth [Trinity 1993] (Box 12)
  - Githens, Sherwood [Education] (Box 12)
  - Glacken, Scotty (Box 12)
  - Glander, Ken [Anthropology] (Box 12)
  - Glasson, William H. [1874 - 1946] (Box 12)
  - Gleckner, Robert F. (Box 12)
  - Glenn, James F. [Urology] (Box 12)
  - Gminski, Mike [Basketball. Retired Jersey, #43] (Box 12)
  - Gobbel, Ellen Huckabee. Gobbel, Luther (Box 12)
  - Godbey, Allen Howard (Box 12)
  - Goestenkors, Gail [Women's Basketball] (Box 12)
  - Goetz, Lou [Basketball] (Box 12)
  - Goffen, Rona (Box 12)
  - Gohdes, Clarence (Box 12)
  - Golding, Martin P. [Philosophy] (Box 12)
  - Goldman, Laurel (Box 12)
  - Goldsmith, Fred [Football Coach] (Box 12)
  - Goldstone, Richard [Law] (Box 12)
  - Goodall, Ellison (Box 12)
  - Goodling, Richard A. [Divinity] (Box 12)
  - Goodson, W. Kenneth (Box 12)
  - Goodwin, Craufurd D. [Economics] (Box 12)
  - Goodwyn, Lawrence C. [History] (Box 12)
  - Gopen, George (Box 12)
  - Gordy, Walter [Physics] (Box 12)
  - Goshaw, Alfred T. [Physics] (Box 12)
  - Gosling, William [Librarian] (Box 12)
  - Gotham, Elizabeth Lucina (Box 12)
  - Gould, Stephen Jay (Box 12)
  - Grabowski, Henry G. [Economics] (Box 12)
  - Graham, Daniel [Economics] (Box 12)
  - Graham, Elizabeth [Library] (Box 12)
  - Graham, John W. (Box 12)
  - Graham, Le Roy E. (Box 12)
  - Grant, Ruth [Political Science] (Box 12)
  - Granville, Joseph [1948] (Box 12)
  - Graves, Thomas W., Jr. (Box 12)
  - Gray, Irving Emery [Zoology, Marine Science] (Box 12)
  - Gray, Gordon (Box 12)
  - Gray, James A. (Box 12)
  - Gray, Kathryn Judd (Box 12)
  - Gray, Kevin (Box 12)
  - Gray, Virginia (Box 12)
  - Green, Robert [Psychiatry] (Box 12)
  - Green, William L. (Box 12)
  - Gregg, Linda (Box 12)
  - Gregg, Robert C. (Box 12)
  - Gregory, Art (Box 12)
  - Greuling, Eugene [Physics] (Box 12)
  - Griffin, Kenneth "Ramon" [TIP] (Box 12)
  - Griffith, William [Administration] (Box 12)
  - Griffiths, Phillip [Provost] (Box 12)
  - Griggs, Lillian (Box 12)
  - Gringle, Rob (Box 12)
  - Grislis, Egil (Box 12)
  - Groat, Dick [Basketball. Retired Jersen, #10] (Box 12)
  - Gross, Paul M. [Education. Chemistry] (Box 12)
  - Grout, Julia R. [Physical Education] (Box 12)
  - Greuling, Eugene [Physics] (Box 12)
  - Grubb, Barbara [Zoology] (Box 12)
  - Grzybowski, Kazimierz [Law] (Box 12)
  - Guillette, Louis (Box 12)
  - Gulley, Wilbur (Box 12)
  - Gurganus, Allen [English] (Box 12)
  - Guthrie, David (Box 12)
  - Guttman, Norman [Psychology] (Box 12)
  - Guttentag, Christoph O. (Box 12)
  - Guy, David [Writer] (Box 12)
  - Guzzardi, Peter [Duke Press] (Box 12)
  - Haas, William E. [Administration] (Box 12)
  - Hacker, Herbert, Jr. [Electrical Engineering] (Box 12)
  - Hadden, William J. (Box 12)
  - Haerle, Col. Peter J. (Box 12)
  - Hagler, Ellis P "Dumpy" [Golf] (Box 12)
  - Haines, Howard N. (Box 12)
  - Halifax, Viscount (Box 12)
  - Hall, F. G. [School of Medicine] (Box 12)
  - Hall, Louise [Art] (Box 12)
  - Hall, Thor [Divinity] (Box 12)
  - Hall, Wayne [Art] (Box 12)
  - Hall, William C. [Anatomy & Psychology] (Box 12)
  - Hall, William Holland [Engineering] (Box 12)
  - Hallowell, John H [Political Science] (Box 12)
  - Haltom, N. Allison [Development] (Box 12)
  - Hamill, R. Wilkins, III (Box 12)
  - Hamilton, Iain [Music] (Box 12)
  - Hamilton, William B. [History] (Box 12)
  - Hammond, Charles (Box 13)
  - Hammond, Sam [Carillonneur] (Box 13)
  - Hammond, W. Michael [Anthropology] (Box 13)
  - Hamner, Ellen (Box 13)
  - Hamner, W. Clay [Business Administration] (Box 13)
  - Hampikian, Aram K. [Electrical Engineering] (Box 13)
  - Han, Moo-Young [Physics] (Box 13)
  - Handler, Philip [Biochemistry] (Box 13)
  - Hanes, Frederic M. (Box 13)
  - Hanes, P. Huber (Box 13)
  - Hanks, John [Music] (Box 13)
  - Hanks, Nancy (Box 13)
  - Hanna, Frank A. [Economics] (Box 13)
  - Hardin, Henry Grady (Box 13)
  - Hardin, Paul [Law] (Box 13)
  - Harer, John [Math. Vice Provost for Academic Affairs] (Box 13)
  - Hargitt, George T. [Zoology] (Box 13)
  - Harmon, Ruth Ann [Maid of Cotton, 1978] (Box 13)
  - Harrar, Ellwood S. [Forestry] (Box 13)
  - Harrington, Milton (Box 13)
  - Harris, Alex [Photography] (Box 13)
  - Harris, Jared (Box 13)
  - Harris, Robert "Bob" (Box 13)
  - Harris, Ross (Box 13)
  - Harrison, Benjamin F. (Box 13)
  - Harrison, Evelyn (Box 13)
  - Hart, Deryl [Medicine, Administration] (Box 13)
  - Hart, Deryl [President] Speeches and Essays (Box 13)
  - Hart, Hornell [Sociology] (Box 13)
  - Hart, Mary Johnson (Box 13)
  - Hartley, Herman O. (Box 13)
  - Hartman, David [1956. Actor] (Box 13)
  - Hartman, Marilyn [Continuing Education] (Box 13)
  - Harvey, J. Oliver [Housekeeping Supervisor] (Box 13)
  - Harward, Stephen C. [Administration] (Box 13)
  - Harwell, George C. [English] (Box 13)
  - Hartwig, Gerald W. [History] (Box 13)
  - Haslam, C. L. [University Counsel] (Box 13)
  - Hauerwas, Stanley [Divinity School] (Box 13)
  - Hauser, Charles [Chemistry] (Box 13)
  - Havely, Robert S. [Director of Government Relations] (Box 13)
  - Harvey, Bill (Box 13)
  - Havighurst, Clark C. [Law] (Box 13)
  - Havrilesky, Thomas [Economics] (Box 13)
  - Hawley, Willis D. [Political Science] (Box 13)
  - Hayes, Helen (Box 13)
  - Hayes, Robin (Box 13)
  - Haynes, Barton F. (Box 13)
  - Haynes, Charlie (Box 13)
  - Healy, Robert [NSOE] (Box 13)
  - Heckscher, William S. [Art] (Box 13)
  - Heinsohn, Paul (Box 13)
  - Heitman, J. F. (Box 13)
  - Heitzenrater, Richard P. (Box 13)
  - Henderson, David [Basketball] (Box 13)
  - Henderson, Elizabeth Aldridge (Box 13)
  - Henderson, James R. [Administration] (Box 13)
  - Henderson, Phil (Box 13)
  - Hendrix, James P. [Medicine] (Box 13)
  - Hendrix, Mildred [Organist] (Box 13)
  - Henney, Richard B. (Box 13)
  - Hendricksen, Gerhard C. [Vice President and Treasurer] (Box 13)
  - Henry, James [Band Director] (Box 13)
  - Henry, Stuart C. [Divinity] (Box 13)
  - Henson, Thomas [Glassblower] (Box 13)
  - Herbert, Dick (Box 13)
  - Herblock [Block, Herb] (Box 13)
  - Herington, C. John [Classical Studies] (Box 13)
  - Herndon, Elaine (Box 13)
  - Heron, Duncan [Geology] (Box 13)
  - Herrick, Allan M. (Box 13)
  - Herring, Herbert J. [Administration] (Box 13)
  - Herron, James Patrick (Box 13)
  - Herzog, Frederick [Divinity] (Box 13)
  - Hetherington, Duncan (Box 14)
  - Heyman, Art [Basketball. Retired Jersey #25] (Box 14)
  - Hickman, Franklin Simpson [Religion] (Box 14)
  - Hicks, Alice Laidlaw (Box 14)
  - Hickson, Arthur O. [Mathematics] (Box 14)
  - High, Sherrill [Grounds Maintainance] (Box 14)
  - Hight, Tim [Engineering] (Box 14)
  - Hildreth, Chris [Director, University Photography] (Box 14)
  - Hill, Dan [Football] (Box 14)
  - Hill, Douglas G. [Chemistry] (Box 14)
  - Hill, Ed [Director, Mary Lou Williams Center] (Box 14)
  - Hill, Grant [1994. Basketball] (Box 14)
  - Hill, Lynn [Student Activities] (Box 14)
  - Hill, Robert L. [Biochemistry] (Box 14)
  - Hillerbrand, H. J. [Divinity School] (Box 14)
  - Hillman, Jennifer [Student on Board of Trustees] (Box 14)
  - Hines, Clarkston (Box 14)
  - Hirschman, Charles [Sociology] (Box 14)
  - Hitchings, George Herbert, Jr. [Nobel Prize] (Box 14)
  - Hobbs, Marcus [Faculty. Administration] (Box 14)
  - Hockaday, Willie [Traffic Office] (Box 14)
  - Hodges, Luther, Jr. [Business Administration] (Box 14)
  - Hogshead, Nancy [Olympic Swimmer. 1984] (Box 14)
  - Holly, Irving B., Jr. [History] (Box 14)
  - Holloway, Benjamin D. (Box 14)
  - Holloway, Karla [Afro-American Studies] (Box 14)
  - Holloway, Russell [Engineering] (Box 14)
  - Holloway, Sim [University Chaffeur] (Box 14)
  - Hollyday, Frederic B. M. [History] (Box 14)
  - Holsti, Ole R. [Political Science] (Box 14)
  - Holt, D. Dillon [Divinity 1933] (Box 14)
  - Holton, Holland [Summer Sessioin] (Box 14)
  - Hoover, Calvin Bryce [Economics] (Box 14)
  - Hopkins, Everett H. (Box 14)
  - Horack, H. Claude [Law. Dean] (Box 14)
  - Horgan, Susan A. (Box 14)
  - Horn, Carl (Box 14)
  - Horowitz, Donald [Law] (Box 14)
  - Horrigan, Edward A., Jr. (Box 14)
  - Hough, Jerry [Political Science] (Box 14)
  - Houpt, Jeffrey L. (Box 14)
  - House, Wendy [Sociology] (Box 14)
  - Howard, John [Director, G. L. B. Center] (Box 14)
  - Howard, Reginaldo Ricardo [ASDU President] (Box 14)
  - Howell, Mary Louise [Payroll] (Box 14)
  - Howser, Jeff [Track] (Box 14)
  - Hoyler, Hamilton (Box 14)
  - Hruska, Allan J. [History] (Box 14)
  - Hubbard, Beth Semans (Box 14)
  - Hubbell, Jay B. [English] (Box 14)
  - Huestis, Charles B. [Administration] (Box 14)
  - Hukabee, Ellen H. [Woman's College] (Box 14)
  - Hudson, Fitzgerald S. [Trustee] (Box 14)
  - Hueckel, Tomasz (Box 14)
  - Huges-Schrader, Sally [Zoology] (Box 14)
  - Hull, Alexander (Box 14)
  - Humm, Harold J. [Faculty. Botany; DUML] (Box 14)
  - Humphrey, Betty [Parapsychology] (Box 14)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H. (Box 14)
  - Humphrey, Kathy (Box 14)
  - Humphreys, Josephine [1967. Author] (Box 14)
  - Hundley, Alice C. [Pianist] (Box 14)
  - Huneycutt, Charles Jerome, Jr. "Jerry" [Football] (Box 14)
  - Hunter, Wanda S. [Faculty, Zoology] (Box 14)
  - Hurlburt, Allan S. [Education] (Box 14)
  - Hurley, Bobby [Basketball. Retired Jersey #11] (Box 14)
  - Huxley, Aldous (Box 14)
  - Hylander, William [Director, Primate Center] (Box 14)
  - Hyatt, Robert P. (Box 14)
  - Hyde, Henry (Box 14)
  - Hyman, Mac [1947. Writer] (Box 14)
  - Inglis, Robert (Box 14)
  - Inman, Walker P., Jr. (Box 14)
  - Irene, Princess of Greece Visit, January 1967 (Box 14)
  - Irving, William [English] (Box 14)
  - Israel, Michael [DUMC] (Box 14)
  - Ivey, George Washington (Box 14)
  - Jackson, James Bennett "Chief" (Box 14)
  - Jackson, Jacquelyn (Box 14)
  - Jackson, Jesse (Box 14)
  - Jackson, Jon [Director, Sports Information] (Box 14)
  - Jackson, Kathleen (Box 14)
  - Jackson, Richard L. [Administration] (Box 14)
  - Jackson, Wallace [English] (Box 14)
  - Jaffe, Louis I. [Trinity 1911] (Box 14)
  - Jakubs, Deborah (Box 14)
  - James, Carl C. [Athletic Director] (Box 14)
  - James, Robert H. [Composer of "Dear Old Duke"] (Box 14)
  - Jameson, Frederic (Box 14)
  - Janiewski, Dolores (Box 14)
  - Jantz, Harold [Germanic Languages and Litarture] (Box 14)
  - Jarboe, Wallace E. [City of Medicine] (Box 14)
  - Jarmul, David [News and Communications] (Box 14)
  - Jarrett, Maria [Student Activities] (Box 14)
  - Jarvis, Thomas Jordan (Box 14)
  - Jayne, Benjamin A., Dr. [Forestry] (Box 14)
  - Jeffrey, Paul [Music] (Box 14)
  - Jenkins, Harry [Sarah P. Duke Gardens] (Box 15)
  - Jenkins, Marianna [Art; Assoc. Dean of Undergraduate Instruction, The Woman's College] (Box 15)
  - Jennings, Robert B. [Pathology] (Box 15)
  - Jennings, William B. [Administration] (Box 15)
  - Jenson, Howard (Box 15)
  - Jentleson, Bruce [Director, Sanford Institute] (Box 15)
  - Jezierski, Bronislas (Box 15)
  - Joerg, Frederick [Assistant Provost] (Box 15)
  - Johns, Sheridan, III [Political Science] (Box 15)
  - Johnson, Allen "Sweet Pea" (Box 15)
  - Johnson, Charles M. D. (Box 15)
  - Johnson, Charles B. [Medical Center Registrar] (Box 15)
  - Johnson, Charles E. [Divinity] (Box 15)
  - Johnson, David (Box 15)
  - Johnson, Kristina [Dean of Engineering, 1999 - ] (Box 15)
  - Johnson, Terry W. [Botany] (Box 15)
  - Johnston, J. Phillips L. (Box 15)
  - Johnston, William H. (Box 15)
  - Johnston, William W. (Box 15)
  - Joines, Bill [Electrical Engineering] (Box 15)
  - Joklik, Wolfgang K. [Microbiology] (Box 15)
  - Jolls, Kenneth R. [Alumnus, 1958] (Box 15)
  - Jones, Alex (Box 15)
  - Jones, Barney L. [Religion] (Box 15)
  - Jones, Edward E. [Psychology] (Box 15)
  - Jones, Edwin L. (Box 15)
  - Jones, Edwin L., Jr. (Box 15)
  - Jones, H. G. (Box 15)
  - Jones, L. Gregory [Dean of the Divinity School] (Box 15)
  - Jones, Jameson [Divinity] (Box 15)
  - Jones, Loring Shaffer, Jr. (Box 15)
  - Jones, Marjorie [Chapel] (Box 15)
  - Jones, Robert Trent (Box 15)
  - Jones, William D. "Big Bill" (Box 15)
  - Jordan, A. C. [English] (Box 15)
  - Jordan, Charles E. (Box 15)
  - Jordan, Brady R. (Box 15)
  - Jordan, B. Everett (Box 15)
  - Queen of Jordan [Queen Noor Al Hussein] (Box 15)
  - Joseph, James [Sanford Institute] (Box 15)
  - Kagawa, Toyohiko (Box 15)
  - Kahane, Meir (Box 15)
  - Kahr, Toby Y. (Box 15)
  - Kain, Tom [Soccer] (Box 15)
  - Kaiser, Helen [Physical Therapy] (Box 15)
  - Kale, William Arthur [Divinity] (Box 15)
  - Kamin, Henry [Biochemistry] (Box 15)
  - Kammerer, Rev. Charlene [Assistant Minister] (Box 15)
  - Kandlbinder, Hans K. (Box 15)
  - Kaplan, Alice [French] (Box 15)
  - Karson, Jeffrey [Geology] (Box 15)
  - Katsouleas, Tom (Box 15)
  - Katz, Samuel [Pediatrics] (Box 15)
  - Katzenmeyer, William G. (Box 15)
  - Kaufman, Wallace (Box 15)
  - Kavass, Igor [Law] (Box 15)
  - Kay, Richard [Anthropology] (Box 15)
  - Keck, Charles [Sculptor] (Box 15)
  - Keefe, Susan A. [Divinity School] (Box 15)
  - Keeler, Brian (Box 15)
  - Keene, Jack D. [Microbiology and Immunology] (Box 15)
  - Keller, Margaret (Box 15)
  - Keller, Thomas E. [Fuqua] (Box 15)
  - Keese, Rev. Peter G. [DUMC] (Box 15)
  - Kelly, Allan C. [Economics] (Box 15)
  - Kelley, William N. [DUMC] (Box 15)
  - Kempner, Walter [Rice Diet] (Box 15)
  - Kenan, Frank Hawkins (Box 15)
  - Kenan, Patrick Dan (Box 15)
  - Kenan, William Rand (Box 15)
  - Kenyon, Van L., Jr. [Mechanical Engineering] (Box 15)
  - Keohane, Robert (Box 15)
  - Keohane, Nan [President]
    - Inauguration clippings (Box 15)
    - Writings (Box 15)
  - Kerckhoff, Alan C. [Sociology] (Box 15)
  - Kerr, Robert Blackburn [Electrical Engineering] (Box 15)
  - Ken, Robert J. [Engineering] (Box 15)
  - Keyworth, George A. [Physics] (Box 15)
  - Kilgo, John C. [President] (Box 15)
  - Killenberg, Paul [M. D.] (Box 15)
  - Killian, James R. (Box 15)
  - Kim, Sung Huo [Biochemistry (Box 15)
  - Kimble, Gregory [Psychology] (Box 15)
  - Kimbrough, Steven [Music] (Box 15)
  - King, Billy [Basketball] (Box 15)
  - King, Garland (Box 15)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr. (Box 15)
  - King, Martin Luther, Sr. (Box 15)
  - King, William E. [Archives] (Box 15)
  - Kinney, Thomas D. (Box 16)
  - Kirkendale, Warren (Box 16)
  - Kirksey, William (Box 16)
  - Kirton, Brenda [Campus Minister] (Box 16)
  - Kiss, Elizabeth [Director, Kenan Ethics Program] (Box 16)
  - Kistler, Doug (Box 16)
  - Kitchen, Dorothy (Box 16)
  - Kitchen, Joseph [Math] (Box 16)
  - Klesch, Gary (Box 16)
  - Klopfer, Peter H. [Zoology] (Box 16)
  - Klutznick, Philip M. (Box 16)
  - Knight, Arthur W. (Box 16)
  - Knight, Douglas M. [President]
    - Biography (Box 16)
    - Inauguration and presidency (Box 16)
    - Resignation (Box 16)
    - Speeches and publications (Box 16)
  - Craig T. Kocher [Associate Dean of Duke Chapel] (Box 16)
  - Koening, Harold [Psychiatry] (Box 16)
  - Kohorn, Bruce [Botany] (Box 16)
  - Koonz, Claudia [History] (Box 16)
  - Kornberg, Allan [Political Science] (Box 16)
  - Korstian, Clarence [Forestry] (Box 16)
  - Kort, Wesley [Religion] (Box 16)
  - Korsarin, Daniel (Box 16)
  - Koskinen, John A. [Trustee] (Box 16)
  - Kossowska, Danuta [Romance Languages] (Box 16)
  - Kramer, Paul J. [Botany]
    - Clippings (Box 16)
  - Kraybill, Edward K. [Dean, Engineering] (Box 16)
  - Kremen, Irwin (Box 16)
  - Kreps, Juanita M. [Economics, Administration] (Box 16)
  - Krigbaum, William R. [Chemistry] (Box 16)
  - Krueger, Robert (Box 16)
  - Kruzel, Hoseph [Political Science] (Box 16)
  - Krynski, John [Slavic Languages] (Box 16)
  - Krynski, Szymon (Box 16)
  - Krzyzewski, Mike [4 folders] (Box 17)
  - Sports Medicine Center, "K Lab" (Box 17)
  - Kulski, Wladyslaw W. [Russian Affairs] (Box 17)
  - Kuniholm, Bruce [Political Science] (Box 17)
  - Kuran, Joseph L. (Box 17)
  - LaBarre, Weston [Anthropology] (Box 17)
  - Lacy, Creighton [Divinity] (Box 17)
  - Ladd, Marcia (Box 17)
  - Laettner, Christian [Basketball. Retired Jersey #32] (Box 17)
  - Lamparter, William S. (Box 17)
  - Land, Kenneth C. [Sociology] (Box 17)
  - Landon, Charles Earl and Helen Knight (Box 17)
  - Lange, Peter [Provost; Political Science] (Box 17)
  - Langford, Thomas A. [Divinity] (Box 17)
  - Lanning, John Tate [History] (Box 17)
  - LaPrade, William T. [History] (Box 17)
  - Larson, Arthur (Box 17)
  - Lassiter, William C. (Box 17)
  - Lattimore, Caroline (Education/Dean/Minority Affairs (Box 17)
  - Latty, Elvin R. "Jack" [Law] (Box 17)
  - Laughhunn, Dan J. [Dean, Graduate School of Business Administration] (Box 17)
  - Lawler, Gregory (Box 17)
  - Lawrence, Bruce B. [History of Religion] (Box 17)
  - Lazewski, Jennifer (Box 17)
  - Leach, Richard H. [Political Science] (Box 17)
  - Leary, Lewis G. (Box 17)
  - Lee, A. Carl [Construction of West Campus] (Box 17)
  - Lee, Eunjin [CHANCE program] (Box 17)
  - Lee, Howard (Box 17)
  - Lee, William S. (Box 17)
  - Lefkowitz, Robert J. [Medicine] (Box 17)
  - Lefler, Hugh T. [Historian] (Box 17)
  - Leftwich, George E., Jr. [Composer, "Blue and White" Fight Song] (Box 17)
  - Leighton, Clare (Box 17)
  - Lemkin, Raphael (Box 17)
  - Lentricchia, Frank (Box 17)
  - Leonard, Debbie (Box 17)
  - Lerner, Warren [History] (Box 17)
  - Leuchtenburg, William E. (Box 17)
  - Levin, Betsy [Law] (Box 17)
  - Levy, Harry (Box 17)
  - Lewin, Arie (Box 17)
  - Lewis, H. Gregg [Economics] (Box 17)
  - Lewis, Harold W. (Box 17)
  - Lewis, Hubert M. "Red" (Box 17)
  - Lewis, M. Modena (Box 17)
  - Leydon, Betty Le Compagnon (Box 17)
  - Lievsay, John L. (Box 17)
  - Lincoln, C. Eric [Religion] (Box 17)
  - Lipscomb, Joseph (Box 18)
  - Lischer, Richard "Rich" [Divinity] (Box 18)
  - Livingstone, Daniel A. (Box 18)
  - Lochmuller, Charles [Chemistry] (Box 18)
  - Lomperis, Timothy (Box 18)
  - Locke, Elizabeth H. "Betsy" (Box 18)
  - London, Edith [Artist] (Box 18)
  - London, Fritz [Physics] (Box 18)
  - Long, Johnny (Box 18)
  - Love, Donald [Hospital] (Box 18)
  - Lowry, Day (Box 18)
  - Lukianuk, Rick (Box 18)
  - Lumiansky, Robert M. (Box 18)
  - Lunsford, Bascom Lamar (Box 18)
  - Lynch, Gary (Box 18)
  - Lynn, Barry (Box 18)
  - Lyon, Lars (Box 18)
  - Lyon, Mary Duke (Box 18)
  - Maddox, George L. [Medical Center] (Box 18)
  - Madey, John M. J. (Box 18)
  - Mahoney, Edward P. (Box 18)
  - Maier, Charles S. [History] (Box 18)
  - Malanga, "Bat" [AnnaMaria's Pizza House] (Box 18)
  - Mallon, William J. (Box 18)
  - Maltese, John Anthony (Box 18)